A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Personal, Series Z FA335
Rockefeller Archive Center
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Personal Papers - Speeches, 1891-1958, n.d.; 8; 8 Document Box(es)
  - Cooperation in Industry, April 1921 (Box 72, Folder 92)
    Institution: International Labor Review Subject: Labor Format: Typed/Magazine article
  - Cooperation: The World's Greatest Need, May 16, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 93)
    Institution: Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) Occasion: Opening of YMCA building Place: Bayonne, New Jersey Subject: Social Welfare Format: Typed/Printed
  - Food for Thought, May 20, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 94)
    Institution: The Messenger Magazine Subject: Social Welfare Format: Magazine article
  - Cooperation, September 28, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 95)
    Institution: Chamber of Commerce Occasion: Meeting of leading Shanghai businessmen Place: Shanghai, China Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed
  - Brotherhood, September 29, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 96)
    Institution: Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) of Shanghai Occasion: Meeting of Shanghai Christian organizations Place: Shanghai, China Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed
  - History and Purpose of Peking Union Medical College, September 29, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 97)
    Institution: Peking Union Medical College Occasion: Dedication of Peking Union Medical College Place: Peking, China Subject: Education Format: Typed
  - A Young Man's Ideals, October 9, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 98)
    Institution: Canton Christian College Place: Canton Christian College Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed
  - Christian Character, October 29, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 99)
    Institution: Philippines Free Press Place: Philippines Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed/Newspaper article
  - Brotherhood, November 14, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 100)
    Institution: Young Men's/Young Women's Christian Association, World Sunday School Association, Woman' Christian College, Federation of Churches Occasion: Union Meeting of World Sunday School Association Place: Tokyo-YMCA building Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed
  - Friendship, November 15, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 101)
    Institution: Tokyo Gazette Occasion: Newspaper interview Place: Japan Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed
  - Report on Trip to Orient - Opening of Peking Union Medical College, December 3, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 102)
    Place: New York City Subject: Education Format: Typed
  - Impressions of China, January 19, 1922 (Box 72, Folder 103)
    Institution: Brown University Occasion: Brown University dinner Subject: Education Format: Handwritten
  - Ideals, January 29, 1922 (Box 72, Folder 104)
  - Accomplishments of Rockefeller Institute, February 20, 1922 (Box 72, Folder 105)
    Institution: Rockefeller Institute Occasion: Anniversary of founding of Rockefeller Institute Place: New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Handwritten/Typed
  - Bible Teaching, April 1922 (Box 72, Folder 106)
    Institution: International Sunday School Association Place: Kansas City, Missouri Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - Impressions of China, April 9, 1922 (Box 72, Folder 107)
    Institution: Westchester County Chamber of Commerce Place: Westchester County Subject: Education Format: Typed
  - So Run That Ye May Obtain, April 9, 1922 (Box 72, Folder 108)
  - A Useful Life, September 27, 1922 (Box 72, Folder 109)
    Institution: Tarrytown Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) Occasion: Father-son banquet Place: Tarrytown, New York Subject: Stewardship Format: Handwritten
  - Home-Made Stewards, November 1922 (Box 72, Folder 110)
    Institution: Layman's New Era Movement Occasion: Authorized interview with John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Place: New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Printed
  - Four Fundamentals of Good Citizenship, November 12, 1922 (Box 72, Folder 111)
  - Letter To The President of the American Petroleum Institute, February 20, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 112)
    Place: New York City Subject: Labor Format: Printed
  - The Greatest Thing in the World, November 4, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 113)
  - Ideals of Standard Oil, November 15, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 114)
    Institution: 26 Broadway Club Place: Astor Hotel, New York City Subject: Labor Format: Typed
  - The Work of the International House, November 18, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 115)
    Institution: Intercollegiate Cosmopolitan Club of New York Occasion: Sunday Supper of Intercollegiate Cosmopolitan Club of New York Place: New York City Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed/Printed
  - Duty, March 11, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 116)
    Institution: Dutch Treat Club Place: Hotel Martinique, New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed
  - Stewardship, April 15, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 117)
    Institution: Chamber of Commerce Place: Wall Street Boys Branch of Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed
  - Responsibility, April 20, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 118)
  - Ideals - International House, November 8, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 119)
    Institution: International House Place: Student's Cosmopolitan Club, New York City Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed/Printed
  - Has Civilization Outgrown Religion, November 30, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 120)
    Institution: Park Avenue Baptist Church Occasion: Young Men's Bible Class Place: New York City Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - Edith Carpenter Macy, April 14, 1925 (Box 73, Folder 121)
    Institution: Cosmopolitan Club, New York City Occasion: Memorial service Subject: Tribute Format: Printed
  - How Can Men Help the Sunday School/How Can a Young Man Serve God?, April 21, 1925 (Box 73, Folder 122)
    Institution: Tarrytown Federated Men's Club Place: Tarrytown, New York Subject: Religion Format: Typed/Printed
  - Education, May 1925 (Box 73, Folder 123)
    Institution: Chamber of Commerce Subject: Education Format: Typed
  - Making a Living or Making a Life, May 7, 1927 (Box 73, Folder 124)
    Institution: Euclid Avenue Baptist Church Place: Cleveland, Ohio Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - Thrift, July 1925 (Box 73, Folder 125)
    Institution: Virginia Bankers Convention Magazine Place: Virginia Subject: Social Welfare Format: Magazine article
  - The Courage to be Different, August 2, 1925 (Box 73, Folder 126)
    Institution: Union Church Occasion: Sunset talk Place: Northeast Harbor Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - The Value of Scholarship in Business, 1926 (Box 73, Folder 127)
    Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed
  - Modesty, Sincerity, January 26, 1926 (Box 73, Folder 128)
    Institution: Park Avenue Baptist Church Occasion: Tribute to Dr. Woelfkin Place: New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Scholarship and Teaching, March 10 & April 12, 1926 (Box 73, Folder 129)
    Institution: Phi Beta Kappa Occasion: Meeting of Phi Beta Kappa/Sesqui-Centenniel Committee dinner Place: Providence, Rhode Island and Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Subject: Education Format: Typed/Printed
  - Creative Wish - Unrecognized Opportunities, May 9, 1926 (Box 73, Folder 130)
    Institution: International House Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed/Printed
  - Peace and Good Will in Industry, December 19, 1926 (Box 73, Folder 131)
    Institution: The McClure Newspaper Syndicate Subject: Labor Format: Reprint from Herald Tribune
  - Brotherhood, January 18, 1927 (Box 73, Folder 132)
    Institution: World Conference Occasion: Luncheon for World Conference Place: Lusanne, Switzerland Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - Business of Being a Father, February 22, 1927 (Box 73, Folder 133)
    Institution: Princeton University Occasion: Alumni Day father's meeting of Princeton undergraduates Place: Princeton, New Jersey Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed/Printed
  - Ideals of Womanhood, May 19, 1927 (Box 73, Folder 134)
    Institution: Spelman College Occasion: Dedication of the Sister's Chapel at Spelman College Place: Atlanta, Georgia Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed
  - Colleges and Tuition, June 15, 1927 (Box 73, Folder 135)
    Institution: Brown University Occasion: Commencement luncheon Place: Providence, Rhode Island Subject: Education Format: Typed/Printed
  - Tribute to Standard Oil Company, November 1927 (Box 73, Folder 136)
    Institution: Fairmont Times Place: West Virginia Subject: Tribute Format: Newspaper article
  - Character - The Foundation of Successful Business, December 1, 1927 (Box 73, Folder 137)
    Institution: 26 Broadway Club Occasion: Dinner of 26 Broadway Club Place: New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed/Printed
  - Contributions of Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), December 8, 1927 (Box 73, Folder 138)
    Institution: Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA)-Tarrytown Occasion: 25th Anniversary of Tarrytown YMCA Place: Tarrytown, New York Subject: Fund Format: Handwritten/Printed
  - Spiritual Values, 1928 (Box 73, Folder 139)
    Occasion: Dictated paragraph Place: Egypt Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - Duty - The Business of Being a Father, March 8, 1928 (Box 73, Folder 140)
    Institution: Lincoln School Place: New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed/Printed
  - High Standards of Business Ethics, April 22, 1928 (Box 73, Folder 141)
    Institution: International House Place: New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed
  - Education, June 6, 1928 (Box 73, Folder 142)
    Institution: Fisk University Occasion: Commencement address Place: Nashville, Tennessee Subject: Education Format: Typed
  - Religious Idealism, October 28, 1928 (Box 73, Folder 143)
    Institution: University of Chicago Occasion: Dedication of University of Chicago chapel Place: Chicago, Illinois Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - Acceptance of Gold Medal Award, April 30, 1929 (Box 73, Folder 144)
    Institution: National Institute of Social Sciences Occasion: Gold Medal Award to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Place: New York City Subject: Personal Format: Printed/Typed
  - Frederick Taylor Gates, May 15, 1929 (Box 73, Folder 145)
    Institution: Rockefeller Institute Occasion: Memorial service Place: New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Industrial Creed of a Capitalist, October 21, 1929 (Box 73, Folder 146)
    Subject: Labor Format: Typed
  - George E. Vincent, November 13, 1929 (Box 73, Folder 147)
    Institution: Rockefeller Foundation Occasion: Meeting of the Rockefeller Foundation Place: New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Friendship, February 6, 1931 (Box 73, Folder 148)
    Institution: Riverside Church Occasion: Testimonial dinner to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Place: University Club, New York Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed
  - Acceptance of The Rosenberger Medal, June 15, 1931 (Box 73, Folder 149)
    Institution: Brown University Occasion: Presentation of The Rosenberger Medal Place: Providence, Rhode Island Subject: Personal Format: Typed
  - Dr. Theobald Smith, November 20, 1931 (Box 73, Folder 150)
    Institution: Princeton University Occasion: Toast Place: Princeton, New Jersey Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Liquor Control - 18th Amendment, June 6, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 151)
    Occasion: Open Letter Place: New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Printed
  - Brotherhood, July 2, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 152)
    Institution: Rockefeller Center Occasion: Laying of cornerstone of the British Empire Building, Rockefeller Center Place: New York City Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed
  - Mrs. Harry Edmonds, January 8, 1933 (Box 73, Folder 153)
    Institution: International House Occasion: Memorial service Place: New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - National Recovery Act, August 26, 1933 (Box 73, Folder 154)
    Institution: National Recovery Act Occasion: broadcast Place: Seal Harbor, Maine Subject: Labor Format: Typed/Printed
  - Soliciting for a Cause, November 14, 1933 (Box 73, Folder 155)
    Institution: Citizens Family Welfare Committee Occasion: Citizens Family Welfare Committee meeting Place: New York City Subject: Social Welfare Format: Typed/Printed
  - Cooperation, February 24, 1934 (Box 73, Folder 156)
    Institution: State of Virginia Occasion: Opening of Capitol building in Williamsburg Place: Williamsburg, Virginia Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed
  - Simon Flexnor / Herbert Gasser, October 7, 1935 (Box 73, Folder 157)
    Institution: Rockefeller Institute Occasion: Retirement of Simon Flexner / Election of Herbert Gasser Place: New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Stewardship, October 12, 1935 (Box 73, Folder 158)
    Institution: City of New York Occasion: Opening of Fort Tryon Park Place: New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed
  - Cooperation, June 30, 1936 (Box 73, Folder 159)
    Institution: French government Occasion: Completion of restoration work in France Place: Versailles, France Subject: Restoration Format: Typed
  - Christian Unity, February 17, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 160)
    Institution: National Broadcasting Company Occasion: Tribute to Dr. E. Stanley Jones, head of National Preaching Movement Place: New York City Subject: Religion Format: Typed/Printed
  - Brotherhood - Peace, February 23, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 161)
    Institution: Park Avenue Baptist Church Occasion: 40th annual dinner of Men's Bible Class Place: New York City Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - Christianity Today, March 7, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 162)
    Institution: Protestant Churches of Tarrytown Occasion: Lenten Service Place: Christ's Episcopal Church, Tarrytown, New York Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - Unemployment Census, November 12, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 163)
    Institution: Federal unemployment census Place: New York City Subject: Labor Format: Typed
  - Brotherhood, November 19, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 164)
    Institution: International House Occasion: 1st Anniversary of Alumni Association of International House Place: International House, New York City Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed/Printed
  - Stewardship, December 30, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 165)
    Institution: Radio City Music Hall Organization Occasion: Tribute to performers of Radio City Music Hall Place: Radio City Music Hall, New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed/Printed
  - Cooperation, February 24, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 166)
    Institution: Greater New York Fund Occasion: Opening rally of The Greater New York Fund Place: Center Theater, New York City Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - Cooperation, April 4, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 167)
    Institution: Chamber of Commerce Occasion: Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce banquet Place: Westchester Country Club Subject: Social Welfare Format: Typed
  - Rufus I. Cole, April 30, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 168)
    Institution: Rockefeller Institute Occasion: Dinner for Dr. Rufus I. Cole Place: Rockefeller Institute, New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Opening of Greater New York Fund Campaign, May 10, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 169)
    Institution: Greater New York Fund Campaign Occasion: Radio broadcast Place: New York City Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - Tribute to Builders, May 10, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 170)
    Institution: The Cloisters Occasion: Opening of the Cloisters Place: New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Stewardship, May 12, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 171)
    Institution: Peking Union Medical College Occasion: China Medical Board dinner Subject: Education Format: Typed
  - Christian Ideals, November 9, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 172)
    Institution: Banker's Club Occasion: New York World's Fair Temple of Religion luncheon Place: New York City Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - Fundraising, March 23, 1939 (Box 74, Folder 173)
    Institution: Greater New York Fund Occasion: Select Gift's Committee of Greater New York Fund luncheon Place: Union Club, New York City Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - Remarks of the Retiring Chairman of General Education Board, April 6, 1939 (Box 74, Folder 174)
    Institution: General Education Board Occasion: Retirement of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. as chairman of General Education Board Place: New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Printed/Report
  - Cooperation in Industry, September 30, 1939 (Box 74, Folder 175)
    Institution: Rockefeller Center Occasion: Meeting of employees of Rockefeller Center/Gymnasium opening Place: Rockefeller Center, New York City Subject: Labor Format: Handwritten/Typed
  - Service to Community, November 1, 1939 (Box 74, Folder 176)
    Institution: Rockefeller Center Occasion: Driving of last rivet in Rockefeller Center Place: Rockefeller Center, New York City Subject: Labor Format: Handwritten/Typed
  - Alcoholism, February 8, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 177)
    Institution: Alcoholics Anonymous Occasion: Dinner in interest of Alcoholics Anonymous Place: Union Club, New York City Subject: Social Welfare Format: Printed/Report
  - Historical Report of Rockefeller Foundation, April 3, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 178)
    Institution: Rockefeller Foundation Occasion: John D. Rockefeller, Jr. retirement as chairman of Rockefeller Foundation Place: New York City Subject: Stewardship Format: Printed/Report
  - James M. Speers, April 30, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 179)
    Occasion: Testimonial dinner Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Reminiscences, October 18, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 180)
    Institution: Union Church of Pocantico Hills Occasion: 25th Anniversary of Union Church Place: Tarrytown, New York Subject: Religion Format: Handwritten
  - Restoration of Williamsburg, November 27, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 181)
    Institution: Rockefeller Foundation Occasion: Staff meeting Place: Williamsburg, Virginia Subject: Restoration Format: Typed
  - Service to Community, November 29, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 182)
    Institution: City of Williamsburg Occasion: Presentation of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. portrait Place: Matthew Whaley High School, Williamsburg, Virginia Subject: Restoration Format: Printed/Typed
  - Brotherhood, December 21, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 183)
    Institution: Rockefeller Center Occasion: Honoring Her Royal Highness Princess Juliana of the Netherlands Place: Rockefeller Center, New York City Subject: Brotherhood Format: Typed
  - Education / Research, April 25, 1941 (Box 74, Folder 184)
    Institution: Chicago University Occasion: 50th Anniversary of Chicago University Place: Chicago, Illinois Subject: Education Format: Typed
  - To Men of Vision and High Purpose, May 3, 1941 (Box 74, Folder 185)
    Institution: Fisk University Occasion: 75th Anniversary of Fisk University Place: Nashville, Tennessee Subject: Stewardship Format: Typed/Printed
  - George E. Vincent, May 19, 1941 (Box 74, Folder 186)
    Institution: New York Academy of Medicine Occasion: Memorial service Place: New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Technique of Soliciting, June 3, 1941 (Box 74, Folder 187)
    Institution: New York City United Service Organizations (USO) Campaign Occasion: Report meeting of Woman's Section of USO Place: New York City Subject: Fund Format: Typed/Printed
  - Soliciting, July 8, 1941 (Box 74, Folder 188)
    Institution: New York City United Service Organizations (USO) Campaign Occasion: Radio broadcast Place: Empire State Building, New York City Subject: Fund Format: Typed/Printed
  - Tribute to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Robert Frances Harper, September 26, 1941 (Box 74, Folder 189)
    Institution: Chicago University Occasion: Citizen's banquet Place: Chicago, Illinois Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - Why I Believe in the USO, March 3, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 190)
    Institution: United Service Organizations (USO) Occasion: USO Field Supervisors Staff Meeting Place: Pennsylvania Hotel, New York City Subject: Fund Format: Handwritten/Typed
  - The USO, Its Background, Origin, Set-up and Why I Believe in It, March 19 & 26, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 191)
    Institution: United Service Organizations (USO) Occasion: Businessmen's dinner/National Woman's Committee Place: 30 Rockefeller Plaza, New York City Subject: Fund Format: Handwritten/Typed/Printed
  - Why I Believe in the USO, May 11, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 192)
    Institution: United Service Organizations (USO) Occasion: Opening of USO Campaign Place: Chicago, Illinois Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - USO Progress Report, May 15, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 193)
    Institution: United Service Organizations (USO) Occasion: USO report luncheon Subject: Fund Format: Typed/Report
  - Spiritual Power, September 27, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 194)
    Occasion: Radio broadcast - Religion Education Week Subject: Religion Format: Typed
  - USO Progress Report - Tribute to Chester I. Barnard, February 4, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 195)
    Institution: United Service Organizations (USO) Occasion: Annual USO meeting luncheon Place: Hotel Astor, New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed/Report
  - Mme. Chiang Kai-Shek, March 2, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 196)
    Occasion: Reception for Mme. Chiang Kai-Shek Place: Madison Square Garden, New York City Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - The USO, Its Task and Opportunity, May 6, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 197)
    Institution: United Service Organizations (USO) Occasion: Dedication of Williamsburg USO Place: Williamsburg, Virginia Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - The USO, May 28, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 198)
    Institution: United Service Organizations (USO) Occasion: National War Fund State Chairmen and Leaders Conference Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - High Standards, August 1943 (Box 74, Folder 199)
    Occasion: Introduction of Mr. Rovensky of Chase Bank Subject: Tribute Format: Typed
  - National War Fund, August 30, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 200)
    Institution: National War Fund Occasion: Radio platter Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - National War Fund and USO, September 16, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 201)
    Institution: National War Fund Occasion: United Service Organizations (USO), National War Fund Conference Place: Pennsylvania Hotel, New York City Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - National War Fund - An Opportunity and a Responsibility, October 4, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 202)
    Institution: National War Fund Place: Chicago, Illinois Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - The Technique of Soliciting and the National War Fund, October 18, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 203)
    Institution: National War Fund Occasion: Women's division meeting of the National War Fund Place: Waldorf Astoria Hotel, New York City Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - Tribute to Leaders of National War Fund, December 17, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 204)
  - Prayer - WOR Radio, January 1, 1944 (Box 74, Folder 205)
  - Personal History - Duty, Service, Sacrifice, February 29, 1944 (Box 74, Folder 206)
  - Tribute to Captain Ware, Commandant of Camp Peary, Virginia, May 2, 1944 (Box 74, Folder 207)
  - Endorsement of United Negro College Fund Campaign, May 26, 1944 (Box 74, Folder 208)
  - The Power to See It Through, September 22, 1944 (Box 74, Folder 209)
    Institution: Minneapolis National War Fund Occasion: Support for National War Fund Place: Coffman Memorial Union, Minneapolis, Minnesota Subject: Fund Format: Typed/Printed
  - The Power to See It Through, October 9, 1944 (Box 74, Folder 210)
    Institution: National War Fund Occasion: Board of Directors Meeting Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - The Power to See It Through, January 29, 1945 (Box 75, Folder 211)
    Institution: National War Fund Occasion: Annual Conference of State United War Fund executives Place: Broad Street Slub, New York City Subject: Fund Format: Typed
  - The Christian Church - What of Its Future?, January 31, 1945 (Box 75, Folder 212)
    Institution: Protestant Council of New York City - 1945 Campaign Occasion: Dinner of Protestant Council of City of New York Place: Waldorf Astoria Hotel, New York City Subject: Religion Format: Typed/Printed
  - Scroll to Richard W. Lawrence / Power to See It Through, February 20, 1945 (Box 75, Folder 213)
    Institution: National War Fund Occasion: National War Fund Annual dinner meeting Place: Hotel Commodore, New York City Subject: Fund Format: Typed